{
  "chapter": 13,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Cloud storage is built upon",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Traditional file system",
        "Cloud native file system",
        "Both a and b",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "In comparison with traditional storage system, the major difference(s) emerge while building cloud storage is",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Supporting scalability",
        "Metering usages",
        "Supporting multi-tenancy",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Cloud native storage file systems are actually virtual in nature. Is this true?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Yes", "No"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "MapReduce framework was built to efficiently process unstructured data in parallel in",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cloud environment",
        "Centralized environment",
        "Distributed environment",
        "Non-cloud environment"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is an open-source cloud file system?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["GFS", "HDFS", "GlusterFS", "KFS"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Unmanaged cloud storages are actually managed by",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Storage provider",
        "Storage consumer",
        "None",
        "Administrator"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Managed cloud storages are generally used by",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Managers",
        "Big enterprises",
        "Application Developers",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "In unmanaged cloud storage user can install applications of his/her choice.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Yes. Till the space permits.",
        "No. They can install only specific applications.",
        "Yes. If the privilege is given.",
        "No. It comes with pre-installed applications."
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "For file hosting purpose, the type of cloud storage used is",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Managed storage",
        "Unmanaged storage",
        "Both a and b",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "There are cloud storage systems which are used to build cloud service and not offered to consumers as a service",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True",
        "False. Cloud storage systems are built to offer as a service to consumers."
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "MapReduce is a",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Storage model",
        "Programming model",
        "File system model",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Google Drive is a",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "General purpose cloud storage",
        "Cloud storage to be used by developers"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    }
  ]
}
